and there, caião,
I'll see you,
smooth. see,
It is fine? I am fine
hell,
I'm accompanying you here.
Man,
look what a talent you've made,
right?
man, I found pasta there
let me show you here.
oh, this boy here,
or guild, or,
sings a lot,
bro,
very much that he came to your talent show.
but he would.
I came by bus,
a big rain now,
the roads
all blocked,
all.
and then guild
me
speak here,
have you ever been on a plane?
have courage?
has courage.
what time will he arrive,
eleven and a half,
tô confirmed.
it's him over there.
How are you doing, brother?
much pleasure.
I fall,
okay,
had a good trip.
,
you
don't like chima
there in the village?
you get chima there you go
ing like this,
with hand,
with the hand. Yes,
you do it here,
Oh,
isn't it?
it's like a bread.
man,
It is that? of course yes
for there you eat and now
and give a smile.
if you have this desire,
we try to see how
can help you,
but that way we can't do everything alone.
being an influencer requires discipline,
Yes,
see it as a job.
and brought the guitar.
they didn't.
They stole his guitar.
the guy is a musician.
he came here,
he doesn't have a guitar.
so I have a surprise for him.
and he doesn't know any of it.
hammer,
.